New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and audiovisual material, 1880 -- 2009; MS099.001; 86.8 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 159 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographs, individuals affiliated with NEMC, 1880 -- 1992; MS099.001.002
    - Rogers, Joseph M.D., MS099.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
    - Rotch, Arthur G., MS099.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
    - Rothney, William, M.D., MS099.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
    - Rubin, S., M.D., MS099.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
    - Sacci, Martha, R.N., MS099.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
    - Saltonstall, Peter, MS099.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
    - Saltonstall, Richard, MS099.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
    - Saltonstall, William, MS099.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
    - Sargent, Mrs. Geroge (Hester), MS099.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
    - Schwartz, William, MS099.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
    - Selverstone, Bertram, M.D., MS099.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
    - Seybolt, Mrs. George, MS099.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
    - Shapiro, Leon N., MS099.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
    - Sherry, Eugene, M.D., MS099.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
    - Sinks, Lucius F., M.D., MS099.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
    - Slater, Robert E., MS099.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
    - Smith, Joseph Tate, M.D., MS099.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
    - Smith, Paul A., Jr., MS099.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
    - Soroff, Harry S., M.D., MS099.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
    - Specter, Benjamin, M.D., MS099.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
    - Spinelli, Viola, MS099.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
    - Stearns, A. Warren, M.D., MS099.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
    - Stimson, Lee (Patient), MS099.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
    - Stockman, Susan, MS099.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
    - Stone, Melvin T., M.D., MS099.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
    - Sullivan, John F., M.D., MS099.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
    - Sullivan, Russell, M.D., MS099.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
    - Talamo, Richard E., M.D., MS099.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
    - Thibodeau, Arthur A., M.D., MS099.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
    - Thompson, Cameron, MS099.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
    - Tilton, Josiah O., M.D., MS099.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
    - Tupper, Earl S., 1968; MS099.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
      - Tupper, Earl, 1968; MS099.001.004.00051.00001; Bachrach (Box 4)
        Portrait of New England Medical Center Hospital benefactor Earl S. Tupper.
        Boston (Mass.); Benefactors; photographic print; Tupper, Earl S.; New England Medical Center Hospital; New England Medical Center
    - Sandra Twyou, MS099.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
    - Viguers, Richard G., MS099.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
    - Walters, Arthur L., M.D., MS099.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
    - Ware, Sheridan, MS099.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
    - Watson, C. Wesley, M.D., MS099.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
    - Weaving, Roger, MS099.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
    - Weinstein, Louis, M.D., MS099.001.004.00058 (Box 4)
    - Weltman, David L., MS099.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
    - Weltman, Mrs. Sol, MS099.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
    - Wien, Janet, MS099.001.004.00061 (Box 4)
    - Williams, Greer, MS099.001.004.00062 (Box 4)
    - Wing, Frank E., 1927; MS099.001.004.00063 (Box 4)
      - Wing, Frank, 1927-03; MS099.001.004.00063.00001; Davis, George H. Jr. (Box 4)
        Director's office. Mr. Wing at desk.
        Boston (Mass.); photographic print; Wing, Frank E.; Boston Dispensary
    - Wolff, Sheldon, M.D., MS099.001.004.00064 (Box 4)
    - Wood, John M., Jr., MS099.001.004.00065 (Box 4)
    - Wren, Paul I., MS099.001.004.00066 (Box 4)
    - Yenetchi, Henry A., M.D., MS099.001.004.00067 (Box 4)
    - Ziskind, Jacob, 1940 -- 1970; MS099.001.004.00068 (Box 4)
      - Jacob Ziskind portrait, 1940 -- 1970; MS099.001.004.00068.00001; Catok, Lotte Meyer (Box 4)
        Portrait by Mrs. Lotte Meyer Catok of Jacob Ziskind, NEMC benefactor.
        Boston (Mass.); Benefactors; photographic print; Ziskind, Jacob (1898-1950); Catok, Lotte Meyer; New England Medical Center
  - Transparencies, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.003
    - Boston Dispensary, Boston Floating Hospital, T-NEMC building, & unidentified, V-3 to V-40, 1920 -- 1930; MS099.001.004.00069 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives.
    - Boston Floating Hospital & unidentified, V-41-V-79, 1900 -- 1920; MS099.001.004.00070 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives. Missing transparencies include V-46, V-54, V-68, V-78. Unidentified transparencies include V-68, V-78.
      Identified transparencies are as follows:
      V-43 - Boston Floating Hospital - naked toddlers on deck, circa 1902 V-44 - Boston Floating Hospital - day patients' open-air ward deck V-52 - Boston Floating Hospital - children and mothers with captain, circa 1903 V-61 - Boston Floating Hospital - children's mealtime on the open air deck, 1920 V-64 - Boston Floating Hospital - food lab bottling mother's milk, circa 1906 V-71 - Boston Floating Hospital - building the new ship V-75 - Boston Floating Hospital - shoeshine boy with life preserver, 1906 V-76 - Boston Floating Hospital - food lab bottling mother's milk, circa 1906
      - Children and mothers with captain, 1903; MS099.001.004.00070.00001 (Box 4)
        Boston Harbor (Mass.); photographic transparencies; Boston Floating Hospital for Infants and Children
      - Children and nurses playing on deck, 1900 -- 1910; MS099.001.004.00070.00002 (Box 4)
    - People, places, Boston Floating Hospital & Boston Dispensary, V-80-V-119, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00071 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives. Unidentified transparencies include V-80, V-110, V-117.
      Identified transparencies are as follows: 84-2-115 V-105 - Boston Floating Hospital - check-in with bag; V-106 - Boston Floating Hospital - nurses tending to babies in the children's ward; and V-111 - Boston Floating Hospital - coming to the Dispensary (Ash Street)
      - On-board check in, 1906; MS099.001.004.00071.00001; T.E. Marr and Son (Box 4)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, Boston Dispensary, people, & unidentified, V-120-V-187, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00072 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives. Unidentified transparencies include V-123, V-142, V-147, V-173, V-187.
      Identified transparencies are as follows: V-126 - Boston Floating Hospital - check in group; V-127 - Boston Floating Hospital - diathermy treatment for pneumonia at on shore department; and V-130 - Boston Floating Hospital - ultra-violet treatment of rickets at on shore department with Dr. Lawrence Smith.
    - Unidentified, Boston Floating Hospital, & Boston Dispensary, V-280-V-394, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00073 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives. Almost all transparencies unidentified.
      Identified transparencies are as follows: V-348 - Boston Floating Hospital - ship between the trees; P-368 - Boston Floating Hospital; P-379 - Boston Floating Hospital - kindergarten photo, circa 1906; P-385 - plans for the New England Medical Center; and P-394 - Boston Floating Hospital - rowboat
      - Mothers and children in dining hall, 1900 -- 1910; MS099.001.004.00073.00001; T.E. Marr and Son (Box 4)
      - Kindergarden class, 1906; MS099.001.004.00073.00002; T.E. Marr and Son (Box 4)
      - The ship between the trees, 1900 -- 1910; MS099.001.004.00073.00003 (Box 4)
    - Unidentified, T-NEMC aerials, V-410-V-947, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00074 (Box 4)
      Identified transparencies are as follows: V-478 - Boston Floating Hospital - open air ward with cribs, nurses, rocking chairs; and V-568 - Boston Floating Hospital - iron lung.
    - Unidentified, V-1085-V-1175, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00075 (Box 4)
    - Unidentified, V-1234-V-1456, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00076 (Box 4)
      Identified transparencies are as follows: V-1453 - Boston Floating Hospital - Reverend Tobey.
      - Hail to the Chief, 1901; MS099.001.004.00076.00001 (Box 4)
        Rufus Tobey holding baby.
        Boston Harbor (Mass.); photographic transparencies; Tobey, Rufus; Boston Floating Hospital for Infants and Children
    - Unidentified, V-1575-V-1750, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00077 (Box 4)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, people, places, unidentified, & Boston Dispensary, P-1767-V-2299, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.004.00078 (Box 4)
      Note that "V" and "P" numbers are indexing numbers from the original NEMC archives. P-2296 is missing.
      - Embarking, 1895; MS099.001.004.00078.00001 (Box 4)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, Boston Dispensary, & unidentified, V-2300-V-2357, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Unidentified, V-2370-V-2599, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
      Identified transparencies are as follows: V-2585 - boy in front of Jackson building, circa 1960.
    - Unidentified, Elaine Ullman, & places, V-2600-V-2677, 1880 -- 1960; MS099.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Educational Media Center, 1894 -- 2000; MS099.001.004
    Images, in various formats, that were produced by NEMC's Educational Media Center. Most of these items are copy prints.
    - Aerial Photographs, MS099.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Activities File, MS099.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Admitting Dept., MS099.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - Allergy and Immunology, MS099.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Anesthesia Dept., MS099.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Anniversaries and Special Events, MS099.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Art, MS099.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Blood Banks, MS099.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Buildings, MS099.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Central Supply, MS099.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Clincal Research Centers, MS099.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Communicable Diseases, MS099.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Community Health Services, MS099.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Dental Services, MS099.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Emergency Medical Services, MS099.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Endocronology, MS099.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Financial Management, MS099.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Food Service, MS099.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - Governing Board, MS099.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Hematology, MS099.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Hemodislysis Units, MS099.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Home Care Services, MS099.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - Hospital Design and Construction, MS099.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Hospital Furniture, MS099.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - Hospital Ships, MS099.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Hospital Volunteers, MS099.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - Housekeeping Department, MS099.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Institutional Management Teams, MS099.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Intensive Care Units, MS099.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Laboratories, MS099.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Location Directories and Signs, MS099.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Maintenance and Engineering, MS099.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Maps, MS099.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Materials Management, MS099.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Medical Education, MS099.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Medical Records Dept., MS099.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Medical Staff, MS099.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Neurology, MS099.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Neurosurgery, MS099.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Nursing Education, MS099.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Nursing Staff, MS099.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Nutrition, MS099.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Occupational Therapy Department, MS099.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Occupational Health Services, MS099.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Opthamology, MS099.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Organizational Affiliation, MS099.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
    - Otolaryngology, MS099.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
    - Outpatient Clinics, MS099.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
    - Pathology Dept., MS099.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
    - Patient Care, 1910 -- 1960; MS099.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - Patients, MS099.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - People, MS099.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - Personnel, MS099.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - Pharmacy Service, MS099.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Phototherapy, MS099.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - Physical Therapy Dept., MS099.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - Places, MS099.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - Play Therapy, MS099.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - Radiology Department, MS099.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Radiotherapy, MS099.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Records, MS099.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Resuscitation, MS099.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Rooming-In-Care, MS099.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Social Work Department, MS099.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - Streets, MS099.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Surgery, MS099.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Surgery Department, MS099.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Telecommunications, MS099.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Urology Department, MS099.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Art, MS099.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Center for Health Communications building, MS099.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Center for Health Communications construction project, MS099.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Center for Health Communications sign, MS099.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary, MS099.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary, MS099.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary Charter, MS099.001.007.00024 (Box Shared 146)
    - Boston Dispensary Clinic, MS099.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary, freeze work on building, MS099.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary, illustrations, MS099.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
    - Boston Dispensary, recommendation slip, MS099.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, MS099.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital "On Shore" Department Milk Laboratory, MS099.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital Infant Ward, MS099.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, aerial view, MS099.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, event, MS099.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, naked toddlers on sundeck, MS099.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, ship, MS099.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
    - Boston, aerial view, MS099.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
    - Chiefs of Staff, MS099.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
    - City Hall Plaza, MS099.001.007.00038 (Box 7)
    - Collins, John; Logue, Edward; unidentified, MS099.001.007.00039 (Box 7)
    - Copley Square, MS099.001.007.00040 (Box 7)
    - Deterling, Ralph, MS099.001.007.00041 (Box 7)
    - Farnsworth Building, MS099.001.007.00042 (Box 7)
    - Government Center model, MS099.001.007.00043 (Box 7)
    - Grossman, Jerome, MS099.001.007.00044 (Box 7)
    - Jackson Memorial Building, fascade, MS099.001.007.00045 (Box 7)
    - Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging, MS099.001.007.00046 (Box 7)
    - Joseph H. Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, MS099.001.007.00047 (Box 7)
    - Joseph H. Pratt Diagnostic Hospital Lab, MS099.001.007.00048 (Box 7)
    - Lawyer for Medical Center, MS099.001.007.00049 (Box 7)
    - Massachusetts State House, MS099.001.007.00050 (Box 7)
    - North Buildling Atrium, MS099.001.007.00051 (Box 7)
    - Nurse and x-ray machine, MS099.001.007.00052 (Box 7)
    - Park Plaza Project, MS099.001.007.00053 (Box 7)
    - Patients & staff, MS099.001.007.00054 (Box 7)
    - Portraits, MS099.001.007.00055 (Box 7)
    - Pratt, Joseph & team, MS099.001.007.00056 (Box 7)
    - Proger, Samuel, MS099.001.007.00057 (Box 7)
    - Sackler Building, model, MS099.001.007.00058 (Box 7)
    - Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, sign, MS099.001.007.00059 (Box 7)
    - Scully Square, MS099.001.007.00060 (Box 7)
    - State Transportation Building, model, MS099.001.007.00061 (Box 7)
    - T-NEMC, aerial view, MS099.001.007.00062 (Box 7)
    - T-NEMC, proposed parking garage, MS099.001.007.00063 (Box 7)
    - Tufts University & Tufts Medical Center insignias, MS099.001.007.00064 (Box 7)
    - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, MS099.001.007.00065 (Box 7)
    - Tufts Univesity School of Medicine, Huntington avenue, MS099.001.007.00066 (Box 7)
    - Tufts Unversity insignia, MS099.001.007.00067 (Box 7)
    - Tupper Research Building, MS099.001.007.00068 (Box 7)
    - Unidentified, MS099.001.007.00069 (Box 7)
    - Unidentified procedures & personnel, MS099.001.007.00070 (Box 7)
    - Aerials (1 of 2), MS099.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Aerials (2 of 2), MS099.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Anatomy (1 of 3), 1980; MS099.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
      Infusion, operations, cross sections.
    - Anatomy (2 of 3), 1980; MS099.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Anatomy (3 of 3), 1980; MS099.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Andrea Zuckerman with unidentified female patient, 1980; MS099.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Center for Health Communications auditorium, 1980; MS099.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
      Graduation ceremony?
    - Brain slides cartoon, MS099.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
      Cartoon reads: "Midway through the exam, Allen pulls out a bigger brain."
    - Brigoli/Welch Nursing Home (1 of 2), 1980; MS099.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
      Unidentified staff and female resident. Welch Healthcare and Retirement Group
    - Brigoli/Welch Nursing Home (2 of 2), 1980; MS099.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Computer screen shot related to integral and differential uniformity, 1989; MS099.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Construction, floor plans, 1984; MS099.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - CT Scan machine (Original label: Ned Sternick), MS099.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Dental care instruction, MS099.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Dissection (Original label: Ruby) (1 of 3), MS099.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - Dissection (Original label: Ruby) (2 of 3), MS099.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Dissection (Original label: Ruby) (3 of 3), MS099.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Goodel and undentified female patient (Original label: DMA - Dr. Goodel), MS099.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Holbert and unidentified female patient (Original label: DMA - Holbert), MS099.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Katya Divari and unidentified female patient (Original label: DMA/Dr. Divari), MS099.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Mitchell Case and unidentified female patient (Original label: DMA - Case), MS099.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Wills and unidentified patient (Original label: DMA/Dr. Wills), MS099.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Equipment, MS099.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Exteriors, MS099.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Floating clinic at Boston high chool, 1990; MS099.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
      Unidentified BFH staff and Boston area high school students.
    - Floating Hospital after snow storm, 1987; MS099.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - From "We Are NE Med", MS099.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
      Unidentified patients and staff, instruments, presentation slides.
    - Glickman portrait painting, MS099.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - Grossman, Jerome (1 of 3), 1988; MS099.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
    - Grossman, Jerome (2 of 3), 1988; MS099.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - Grossman, Jerome (3 of 3), 1988; MS099.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - Historical images, MS099.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - Instruments (1 of 4), MS099.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - Instruments (2 of 4), MS099.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
    - Instruments (3 of 4), MS099.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
    - Instruments (4 of 4), MS099.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
    - Interiors (1 of 2), MS099.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
    - Interiors (2 of 2), MS099.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
    - Medical education cartoons for children, MS099.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
    - New England Medical Center insignia, MS099.001.008.00040 (Box 8)
    - Oil painting of original Boston Floating Hospital (1 of 2), MS099.001.008.00041 (Box 8)
    - Oil painting of original Boston Floating Hospital (2 of 2), MS099.001.008.00042 (Box 8)
    - People, MS099.001.008.00043 (Box 8)
      Doctors, nurses, patients, staff.
    - Sailing, MS099.001.008.00044 (Box 8)
    - Sensational medical headlines, MS099.001.008.00045 (Box 8)
    - Skull, MS099.001.008.00046 (Box 8)
    - Tecle lab, MS099.001.008.00047 (Box 8)
    - Transplant team final brochure photos, MS099.001.008.00048 (Box 8)
      Individual portraits of doctors are labeled.
    - Tufts University Medical School historic images, MS099.001.008.00049 (Box 8)
    - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine insignia, MS099.001.008.00050 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified doctor and elderly patient (Original label: Infusion Center), 1980; MS099.001.008.00051 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified doctor and male patient (Original label: NEHA Retakes) (1 of 2), 1980; MS099.001.008.00052 (Box 8)
      New England Healthcare Assembly?
    - Unidentified doctor and African-American child (Original label: NEHA Retakes) (2 of 2), 1980; MS099.001.008.00053 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified doctors, nurses, patients (Original label: Nursing home brochure cover), 1980; MS099.001.008.00054 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified infant (Original label: Stan Schwartz), 1980; MS099.001.008.00055 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified nurse, child, parent (Original label: Pedi/walk-in clinic), 1980; MS099.001.008.00056 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified portrait painting, MS099.001.008.00057 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified slides of presentation by Dr. Schelling, MS099.001.008.00058 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified slides of presentation regarding mining and radiation (Original label: Obesity Clinic), MS099.001.008.00059 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified staff and patient (Original label: NE Eye/Color slides), MS099.001.008.00060 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified slides of presentations and promotional material (1 of 4), MS099.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
      These slides are unidentified and unlabeled. Many slides are probably duplicates, and/or are possibly related to slides that are cataloged earlier in the series. Slides appear to cover presentations, as well as marketing material related to NEMC/T-NEMC. These slides are copyrighted.
    - Unidentified slides of presentations and promotional material (2 of 4), MS099.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Unidentified slides of presentations and promotional material (3 of 4), MS099.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Unidentified slides of presentations and promotional material (4 of 4), MS099.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Physicians and staff, 1980 -- 1990; MS099.001.321.00001 (Box 321)
    - Physicians and staff, 1980 -- 1990; MS099.001.321.00002 (Box 321)
    - Historic photos, 1894 -- 1950; MS099.001.321.00003 (Box 321)
    - Vital Signs, 1987; MS099.001.321.00004 (Box 321)
    - Public Affairs Vital Signs, 1987; MS099.001.321.00005 (Box 321)
    - Vital Signs, 1987; MS099.001.321.00006 (Box 321)
    - Reception for Italian doctors, Wang Center development, 1987; MS099.001.321.00007 (Box 321)
    - Breast Health Center opening, 1987; MS099.001.321.00008 (Box 321)
    - Hackford, Andy, 1987; MS099.001.321.00009 (Box 321)
    - Mel Goldman color sitting, 1987; MS099.001.321.00010 (Box 321)
    - Caira, Bob, 1987; MS099.001.321.00011 (Box 321)
    - Bank of Boston employee cocktail party, 1987; MS099.001.321.00012 (Box 321)
    - Bakan, Joe, 1987; MS099.001.321.00013 (Box 321)
    - Michael, Constantine, 1988; MS099.001.321.00014 (Box 321)
    - Richmond, John, 1987; MS099.001.321.00015 (Box 321)
    - Orthopedic residents, 1987; MS099.001.321.00016 (Box 321)
    - Medicine residents, 1987; MS099.001.321.00017 (Box 321)
    - Pediatric residents, 1987; MS099.001.321.00018 (Box 321)
    - Rothchild passport, 1987; MS099.001.321.00019 (Box 321)
    - Sheils, Kathy, 1987; MS099.001.321.00020 (Box 321)
    - Cohen, Cecile, 1987; MS099.001.321.00021 (Box 321)
    - Pathology group photo, 1987; MS099.001.321.00022 (Box 321)
    - Pediatric GI group, 1987; MS099.001.321.00023 (Box 321)
    - Pandian, Nat, 1987; MS099.001.321.00024 (Box 321)
    - Pediatric house staff, 1987; MS099.001.321.00025 (Box 321)
    - Selker, Harry, 1987; MS099.001.321.00026 (Box 321)
    - Brent, Vera, 1987; MS099.001.321.00027 (Box 321)
    - Jos Byrne Charlton lecture, 1987; MS099.001.321.00028 (Box 321)
    - Borell, Merriley, 1988; MS099.001.321.00029 (Box 321)